Instead, let's get an awesome souvenir and go to New York!
...to radically oppose the Russo family...
AMAZING!!
MAZING!!
AZING!!
それでは諸君 紹介しよう…
Well then, gentlemen, let me introduce them to you.
These are FBI Special Investigators Bill Sullivan and Donald Brown.
こちらは連邦捜査局 特別捜査官
ビ丿しサリバン氏と
ドナ丿しドブラウン氏だ…
よろしく
Nice to meet you.
Yeah...
ああ…
よろしく…
Nice to meet you.
お二人は複数の州に
またがって起きている
They have been chasing after the suspects of serial robberies in several states.
連続強盗事件の
容疑者を追つてこられた
The amount of cases has risen above 110, and I want to help them in any way I can.
被害 は80件以上 に のぼつ て お り
私としては
署をあげて協力するつもりだ
これがその強盗犯の写真だ
These are some pictures of the robbers.
次
Next.
Chief.
署長…
何かね?
Yes?
Are you screwing with us?
ふざけておられるのですか?
もつともな質問だが
ふざけているのは この連中だ
A very good question. However, the only people screwing around are those in the pictures.
Chief.
署長…
何かね?
Yes?
これだけ写真に撮られていながら
なぜ逮捕できなかつたのですか?
Even though they've been caught on so many pictures,
why hasn't anyone been able to arrest them?
もつともな質問だが
Another very good question. We'll have Mr. Sullivan explain that to us.
それについては
サリバン氏から説明してもらおう
ンンツ
A couple of citizens intrigued by their eccentric outfits took these pictures by chance.
これらは彼らの奇抜な格好を
珍しカヾった地元の人間が
たまたま撮影したものです…
彼らが強盗およぴ窃盗犯であることが
分かつたのは
The citizens usually didn't know they were suspects of theft and robbery until after they had taken the pictures.
たいてい撮影後のことです
Until now, their crimes had been too petty, so they rarely appeared on our investigation list.
今までの犯行は微罪すきて
我々の捜査リス卜にも
なかなか引つかかつて
きませんでした
Petty things like clocks, chocolate, candy... and...
時計 チヨコレ一卜
キヤンデイ一 それと…
美術館の扉を盗んだという程度です
They stole the door of a museum once.
Then... Wouldn't it be better if we just let their mothers scold them?
それならママに 舵つてもらつたほうが
早いのではありませんか?
そうとばかりも言つてられんのだ…
We can't just leave it at that.
They stole all of the assets of New Jersey's millionaire family, the Genoards!
連中は二ユ一ジヤ一ジ一の富豪
ジ工ノア一ド氏の遺産を
そつくり奪つていつたのです!
Chief.
署長…
何かね?
Yes?
急にどうしちやつたんでしようねえ
Why have they changed all of a sudden?
もつともな質問だが
私に聞かれても困る…
Another very good question, but I don't know.
当人たちに聞いてくれたまえ…
You should ask them yourself.
しまったああああ
ミリアア一一ツ !
Damnit!
Miria!
俺たちは大変なことを忘れてたぞ…
We have forgotten something very important.
何のこと?
What are you talking about?
For Ennis... For Ennis!
工二スにイ !
工二スにイ一一一!
ム⓪口~~…
W-W-What should we do?!
どどどどどうしよう…
How can we fix this mistake?!
どうすり やいいんだあああ一一一一つ !
アイザツクう一一一!
Isaac!
Miria!
三リアアアア!
ぐあしつ!
We've forgotten to buy a souvenir for Ennis!
工二スに お土産買うの
忘れたあ一一っ !
おい みんな
Hey, all of you.
前の連結の所に何かいる
There's someone out front near the coupling between the train cars.
One, two.
せ一の
Rail Tracer...
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一
It disappeared.
もう見えない
Let's go.
行こう
Just maybe...
もしかしたら…
上つてみよう!
Let's climb up.
ド二一は下から通路を進んで
ーつ前の連結部で待ってて
Donny, you go and walk through the gangway below.
Wait at the next coupling.
You can count on me.
任せろ…
黒服には くれぐれも気をつけてね
And watch out for the black-suits.
ぬあっ !
All right.
行こう
Let's go.
Sis, Jacuzzi got all fired up, didn't he?
姐さん ジヤグジ一の奴
ひよつとしてキてますよね?
フツ 丿しツソファミリ一の奴らに
8人殺された時以来です
Yeah, it's the first time since we had eight of our friends killed by the Russo family.
あんときゃ泣きながら
すごかつたよなア…
Though he was crying, he sure was amazing then.
How far he'll go this time, no one can tell.
今度は どこまで行くのやら…
俺は丿しノラ一夕フア三リ一の
グス夕一ヴォバジ工ツ夕だ…
I am Gustavo Baggetta of the Runorata family.
手荒なマネをしたが
命まで取る気はないから安心しなm
Sorry for our rough behavior earlier, but we won't kill you, so relax.
Runorata... I have heard about you.
丿しノラ一夕…
聞いたことがあるわ…
あんたの 峯さんも親父も兄貴も
うちのボスと脹零だつたからな…
That's because your grandpa, your old man, and your brother were on familiar terms with my boss.
ハツ ハツハツ ハツハツハツ
どうして
こんなことをするんですか?
Why are you doing this?
I have business with your beloved brother.
あんたの下の兄貢に用があってね…
With Dallas-niisan?
ダラス兄さんに?
That Dallas has pulled a little prank.
そのダラス兄さんが
おイ夕をしたのさ…
叱つてやらなきゃならねぇが
どこにいるのか さっぱり分からねぇ
I have to scold him a little for that, but we have no clue where he is right now.
そこで あんたを人質に…
野郎をおびき出そうって寸法さ…
So we've taken you hostage, and we hope to draw him out.
イヤでも しばらく
付き合ってもらうぜ…
We'll have you stay with us for a little while even if you hate it.
You scared?
怖いか?
怖いんだな…
You're scared, right?
You're a tough little missy.
気の強い嬢ちやんだ…
お前の兄貴が どんなおイ夕をしたか
教えてやろうか?
Shall I tell you what kind of prank Dallas has pulled?
ゆすつてきたのさ…
He's been blackmailing me by saying that I killed your father and brother!
俺があんたの親父さんと兄貴を
殺したってなァ一一!
それは本当ですか?
Is that true?
本当にあなたが
父とジ工フリ一兄さんを?
Have you really killed Father and Geoffrey-niisan?
フツ… 教えてやらない…
I won't tell you.
あんたはホン卜に あのへ夕レ親父や
へ夕レ兄貴と血がつながってるのか?
Are you really related to that pathetic father and brother of yours?
あいつらに あんたほどの
気の強さがありゃあ
If they had been as tough as you,
あと5分は
長生き できただろうにな…
they would probably have been able to live five minutes longer.
Oops, that was a slip of the tongue there.
おおっと…
こいつはロがすベったな…
God punishes people like you.
あなたのような人には
神様が罰を与えて下さいます…
神様だア ?
God?
力のある人間が勝つ…
それがこの世のお彗てだ…
People with strength win. That is the law of this world.
That's not true!
そんなことない!
Dallas-niisan.
ダラス兄さん…
Hey, Miria.
おい 三リア
なあに ? アイザツク
What, Isaac?
She's crying.
泣いてるぞ…
泣いてるね…
She's crying, indeed.
She's looking at the picture and crying.
与真 見て泣いてるなぁ
フオ 卜グラフイ一だね…
It's a photograph.
It must be of her lover.
きっと恋人だ…
It's a romance.
ロマンスだね !
ラブラブだったんだなあ…
They must've been all lovey-dovey.
ラブラブだねえ !
They're all lovey-dovey!
生き別れになつたのかなぁ?
Maybe they were separated.
It must've been a very sad separation.
きつと すつごい悲しい
別れだったんだね!
それとも死に別れかな?
Or it could've been that he died...
Such a tragic love...
悲恋だね…
Excuse me?
あの一…
Shhh!
シ一一一ツ
ググッ なぜ分かつた!
How did you know?!
どうして分かつた !
Why did you know?!
聞こえていたから…
I could hear you.
ひはああああ…
どうする? 三リア
What do we do, Miria?
手ごゎい相手だね !
She's a tough opponent!
You know what we are? We're robbers!
俺たちはなア一 強盗だあ~~ !
強盗だあ~ !
Robbers!
うつ… ふ ふふ…
おいっ 笑つてるぞ…
She's laughing...
うん 笑つてるね…
She really is laughing...
さっきまで泣いてたのに~
But she was crying until just now...
That sure is a sudden turn.
急転直角だね…
だつて おかしいんだもの…
くつ くつ…
You two are strange after all.
Well then, we are left with no choice.
ならば仕方がない…
仕方がないね…
There's no choice.
Let us hear the story about your lover!
君の恋人の話を
聞かせてもらおう!
It's life advice!
人生相談だね !
Lまぁ‥
相談に乗るぜ !
We'll guide you along.
We don't lie!
オラたち ウソつかない
とうだつた?
How is it?
見張りヵヾ2人いて
両方とも機関銃を構えて それで…
There are two guards, and they're both carrying machine guns, and...
私たちの周りにいた人たちが
そろつて消えてる…
The people who were around us completely disappeared...
Mr. Isaac, Ms. Miria, Czes-kun, Meri-chan, and Mrs. Beriam, they're all gone.
アイザツクさん 三リアさん チ工ス君
メリ一ちやんにベリアムさん…
みんないないの
No way...
そんな‥
どこかに連れていかれたのかも…
They might've been taken somewhere else.
捜さなきや…
ええ?
We have to look for them.
二一スと二ックは屋根から
食堂車の向こうへ行って
Nice and Nick, you two go over the roof to the other side of the dining car.
ド二一は僕と
うむ
You're with me, Donny.
二一ス… 絶対に戻ってくるから
無理しないで…
Nice, we'll definitely come back, so don't do anything crazy.
え!? 兄イ~~!?
Eh? Brother?!
Yes...
はい… 本当はダラス兄さんは
とても心の優しい人なんですm
Dallas-niisan is really very kind at heart...
However, lately he's gotten a little rough,
け ど最近 ちよっと荒れてぃz
あまり家にも帰つてこなくて…
and he doesn't really come home often...
He's gotten rough, apparently.
荒れてるそうだ
不良少年だね
He's a juvenile delinquent.
However... Why?
しかし何で?
うちはその… お金持ちなんです
We are... quite rich.
Isn't that a good thing?
いいこと じやないかぁ !
いいことだね !
It's a good thing!
そうでもないんです川
That isn't entirely true.
Whether or not it is because we are blessed,
うちが恵まれているせいか
人が うわベだけで付き合つていたり
there are people who just support us on the surface.
What they think differs from what they say...
言つてることと
思つてることが違つてぃたりm
見たくないものも色々と見えて…
We see a lot of things we don't really want to see.
兄はたぶん それで…
Probably, as a result, my brother...
難しいなァ~~
That's so difficult.
難題だね
It's a difficult problem.
What should we do?
どうすりゃいい?
それならいつそ
お金持ちでなくなれば?
Maybe you should just stop being rich?
そうすりゃイヤなものを
見ないで済む!
If you do that, you won't have to see those things anymore!
簡単だねつ !
Then it's easy!
ちよつと失礼!
失礼!
Excuse us for a moment.
Excuse us.
さらに失礼 !
Excuse us even more.
I wonder what happened here, Miria.
これは どういうことなんだろぅなぁ
三リァ
三ステリ一だね…
It's a mystery.
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一かな…
Maybe it was Rail Tracer?
うつ‥ ホラ_だね
It's a horror.
ジヤグジ一はどこに…
Where is Jacuzzi?
どうしよう…
もう食ベられちゃったんじや…
What should we do?! Maybe he's been eaten already?!
だだ 大丈夫だって!
H-He's all right!
死体がないつてことは
Since his corpse isn't here, he's probably been swallowed by the monster.
その怪物に
飲み込まれちまつたのガもなァ~…
だからまだ腹ん中で生きてるつて…
So he's still alive in his stomach!
丸飲みなんだね…
あ一 よかつたぁ一…
He's swallowed whole then.
I'm so happy!
丸飲みだつてええええ!?
Swallowed whole, you say?!
Swallowed whole?!
丸飲みイ !
うわつ あ~~~
食ゎれちまいやがつてえええ…
Getting eaten like that...
でもでも ジヤグジ一を食ベちやつた奴が
どこにいるのか分からないよぉ~~
But, but... We don't know where the creature that ate Jacuzzi is...
あぁ 大丈夫さ
この列車に乗つていれば…
It's all right.
As long as it's on this train, we're together with Jacuzzi!
ジヤグジ一と 一緒つてことさ…
うん… 心の中で
生きてるってことだよね
Living on inside our hearts, right?
ミリアさあ~~ん!
Ms. Miria!
ホン卜 いい奴だつた…
He really was a great guy!
いい奴だった
うん…
A great guy!
無事でしたか一一
You're all right?!
天国のジヤグジ一 ありがとう…
Jacuzzi from the heavens, thank you!
Mr. Isaac!
アイザツクさぁ一一ん !
ああ… こうして俺のことを
呼んでくれる彼の声を
His voice, which is calling for me...
ぬお?
どああっ !
I won't be able to hear it...
もう二度と聞くことは…
きやあ~~!
A-ga-in...
でき… な いんだ!
なあ一一一つ !
よ よかつたぁ…
2人とも無事だったんですね…
I'm glad!
I see the two of you are all right.
ジヤ… ジヤグジ一こそ
無事で何より…
I'm glad you're all right as well, Jacuzzi.
You came out of his stomach, right, Jacuzzi?
おなかから出てきたんだね
ジヤグジ一!
おなか ?
Stomach?
と と とりあえず この部屋から出て
貨物室に行きましよう…
Anyway, let's leave this room for now and go to the luggage room.
Okay, let's go!
よし 行こう!
そうか 分かったぞ
I see... I understand now.
この列車… 今や…
This train is... just like the Romance of the Three Kingdoms!
サンゴクシつてワケだな…
R-Romance of the Three Kingdoms?!
サ… サンゴクシ…
サンゴクシつて?
And the Romance of the Three Kingdoms is?
サンゴクシつてのは
中国の有名な歴史さ !
The Romance of the Three Kingdoms is a famous part of Chinese history.
すんごいサムライが国を3つに分けて
いがみあったつて話よ!
Three amazing samurai divided the country in three and fought each other.
And?
If I'm not mistaken, they were Sousou, Ryuubi, and... Hokusai!
確か ソ一ソ一とリユ一ビと
ホクサイだ…
They are often compared to a snake, a slug, and a frog, right?
それつて よくへビとナメクジと
力工ルに例えられるよね…
Slug?
ナメクジ?
だからジヤグジ一!
お前はヨシツネになれっ !
So, Jacuzzi, you have to turn into Yoshitsune!
Yoshitsune was a general of the Minamoto clan of Japan in the late Heian and early Kamakura period, completely unrelated to the Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
なれつ !
Turn into!
ぼ 僕がそんなすごい人に ?
M-Me turn into someone so amazing?!
You can!
なれるって!
なれるよ !
あ 乗客のみんなは必ず助けるし
I will definitely save all the passengers,
黒服もルッソの奴らも
やつつけるつもりです…
and I want to take care of the black-suits and the Russo family as well,
でも僕は
そんな立派な人じゃないよ…
but I'm not that magnificent.
お酒も造つてたし 昨巳だって
人を3人も殺したんだ…
I've been making alcohol,
and I killed three people yesterday.
殺したア!?
You killed?!
違う ! 殺したのは俺たち
ジヤグジ一はやつてない!
You're wrong! We were the ones who killed them! You didn't do it, Jacuzzi!
同じことだよ…
It comes down to the same thing.
僕たち 丿しツソファ三リ一{こ
仲間を8人も殺されたんです…
We had eight of our friends killed by the Russo family.
They were killed?!
殺されたア!?
それで僕 頭にきて
So I went mad and robbed eighteen of the Russo family's stores!
ー人で丿しツソファミリ一の店を
ー8軒 強盗して…
E-Eighteen?!
じゆ ー8軒!
That should take like a month!
ひと月がかり だね !
いえ! ー巳です!
In one day!
In one day?!
ー巳イ!?
Jacuzzi was ten times as fearful as normal.
ジヤグジ一
いつものー0倍 恐ろしかつた…
う そして いつものー00倍
泣いていた…
And he cried a hundred times more than normal.
奴ら!まか鱒きだけど でも結局…
It was revenge for my friends, but in the end,
ぼ… 僕が余計なことをしたから
また人を殺すことになつたワケで…
because I did such unnecessary things,
we had to kill yet more people...
だ… だから僕なんか
立派な人間じゃないし…
Thats why I'm not such a magnificent person.
うつ う うゎつ!
そんなこと気にすんなつてえ一 !
Don't let such things get to you!
Sousou and Yoshitsune have killed thousands, millions, billions of people!
だって
ソ一ソ一だつて ヨノノネ
何人も何万人も何億人も何兆人も
殺してるさ!
If the people around them say they're good people, they become good people!
それでも周りのみんなが
いい奴だって言えば
いい奴になるんだよお一一つ !
まぁ つまりアレだア…
In other words, it's like that.
You have to ride the waves of the time!
その場のノ ー丿 だね…
That's it!
それだア一一つ !
So... Jacuzzi, we're saying you're a good guy.
だからよ一一 ジヤグジ一
俺らは お前がいい奴だつて言つてんだ
その波に乗り遅れんなよ !
Don't get to riding that wave too late!
反対する奴がいても
If there are people who say different, just let 'em be drowned by the waves!
逆に この流れに
巻き込んじまえばいいのさ !
でもね でもね
その波を起こすにはね
But, but! It's necessary for at least one of the people around you...
周りの人力ヾー 人でもいい人だつて
思うことが 必要なの!
to think you're a good person in order to cause the waves.
私たちが知つてるの !
And we know!
だから私たちヵヾ
波を起こしてあげるの!
So that's why we will cause the waves for you!
ね
つ! なツー
Okay?!
ありがとう…
Thanks.
やあ
Hey.
君んちの不幸は
俺たちがみんな持ってってやる!
We'll take all of the misfortune of your house!
これで一家安泰だねつ !
With this, your house is secure!
Your brother will surely get back on his feet again as well.
兄さんもきっと
立ち直るぞお一一一一!
It's rehabilitation!
更生だね !
じや
Well then.
あ あ あの
E-Ehm...
そうだ… 君の名前は?
Oh, right. What's your name?
イブ… イブジ工ノア一ド…
Eve. Eve Genoard.
イブ 君はきつと幸せに…
Eve, you can definitely become... happy!
なれる!
Become happy?
幸せに ?
じや
See you.
ふつ… フフフフフ…
じや…
See you.
どこに行くんです?
Where are you going?
もちろん
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一を捜しにさ!
We're going to look for Rail Tracer, of course!
この列車から帰ってもらうように
お願いするの!
We're going to ask him if he can leave this train and go home!
ダメだつたら?
What if he doesn't listen?
やつつける !
We'll take care of him!
それでもダメだったら?
And if that doesn't work either?
う一ん…
We'll flee and hide!
逃げて隠れる !
That monster must be strong.
うつ 化け物きっと強い… 殺される
You'll get killed.
平気さ ! いざとなつたら !
We'll be all right!
If things take a turn for the worse...
フ一一一… 俺の百丁拳銃で…
I'll use my hundred guns!
一丁もないじゃないですか!
You don't even have one?!
確かになア…
Indeed...
However, a gunman from the past used to say this:
だがすァ~ 昔のガンマンは
こう言つたせえ~
銃は みんなの心の中にある…
っzな
"There's a gun in everyone's heart."
死んじやダメだからね !
Don't die now.
See you.
じや…
What a whimsical and self-centered duo.
なんてワガママで
自分勝手な人たちなんだろう…
They're more heinous than I am.
あの2人は僕なんかより
よつぽどの悪党だよ…
行こう…
僕らもワガママを通しに…
Let's go. We have to show our selfishness as well.
Let's become the biggest villains on board this train while we're at it.
どうせなら この列車で
一番の悪党になってやろうよ!
ぬわぁ… 楽しそうだな
ジヤグジ一
That sounds like fun, Jacuzzi.
これでおしまいだな!
We're done now, right?
Done, right?
おしまいだね !
しっかしこの車 俺たちを
はね飛ばしたのと そつくりだなあ!
But this car looks just like the one that hit us!
そつくりだね !
Just like it!
あの‥ 実Lま‥
Well... Honestly...
No... It's nothing.
いや… 何でもないです…
ところで姉ちゃん こいつら
どこに連れていくんだ?
By the way, Sis, where are you taking them?
えっ? 警察に…
Eh?
To the police.
I see...
そつかァ~~…
んじやあ お別れだなァ~~
Then we'll have to say goodbye.
It's a shame.
残念だね~
What's the matter?
どうされたんです?
The police are a little too...
警察は ちよつとなア一
We'll get caught...
捕まつちやうもんねえ~~
Well, if you insist, we're doing something of a journey to atone for our sins.
まァ しいて言えば 俺たち
償いの旅をレてるようなもんかなァ~
We're going to compensate for the large amount of bad things we did.
悪いこと たっくさんした分
いいことするの!
I see.
そうですか…
お二人は強いんですね…
You two are quite strong.
Eh?
ああ そう 俺は強いよ!
Ah right, I'm very strong!
We're strong!
強いよ !
I'm too afraid to face my own sins.
私は自分の罪と向き合うことが
怖くて仕方ありません…
What's wrong, Sis?
何だよ 姉ちやん…
何か悪いことしたのかァ~?
Did you do something bad?
えっ 人を
I...
I don't know what happened, but...
!可力ヾあったヵ知らなぃけどよお
You saved us just now, didn't you?!
さつき俺たちを
助けてくれただろ?
So let's call it even with that!
それでチヤラつてことにしようよ !
うん! 悪人はどれだけ
悪いことをしても
No matter what kind of bad things a bad person has done,
ー個いいことをすれば みんな
if he then does something good, people might think he's actually a good person!
あいつ実は
いい奴かも しれないつて思つちやうの !
だからチヤラ !
That's why you're even now!
ねつ!
Okay?!
あ… ありカヾとう…
Thank you.
私 もう行きますね
I'm going now.
Ah, I see.
ああ そぅか
あ 俺はアイザツクデイアン
I'm Isaac Dian.
And I am Miria Harvent.
私はミリアハ一ヴ工ン卜 !
あ… 私は… 工二ス
名字はないの…
I am Ennis. I don't have a last name.
I see... You don't have a last name?
あ そつかぁ 名字はないのか…
変わつてんなぁ!
You're a strange one!
覚えたよ… 工二ス 工二スだね!
I'll remember it. Ennis!
It's Ennis, right?!
じゃあな 工二ス一!
See you, Ennis!
じやあね一 !
See you!
おお~~い!
Heeey! See you again!
またな一一 !
Let's meet again!
また会おうねえ一一つ !
Bye-bye!
ばいばあ一一い !
またね…
See you.
イブ
Eve...
Eve!
ああっ ダラス兄さん…
Dallas-niisan!
It's been a long time.
く誓ラ蓼!
じ無沙汰だつたな…
どうだ? 今夜あたり
How about I teach you some billiards tonight? It's been a while.
久しぷりに
ビリヤ一 ドでも教えてやろうか?
It's terrible!
大変だ! 泥棒力ヾ!
Thieves have...
見てくるよ
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
やめろよ お祈りなんて!
Stop that praying of yours!
They say a thief was here.
泥棒だとよ やつてらんねえよ
I can't do this...
せつかく爺さんの遺産が入つたガら
小遣いせぴりに帰ってきたのによォ !
I only came by to ask for some allowance since Grandpa's inheritance had arrived, but...
Brother...
兄さん…
You sure are an idiot for believing in God.
お前も神様なんて信じてると
バ力見るぜ!
ハツ
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Claire Stanfield Faithfully
Carries Out the Mission
Hey, Isaac, who is Claire?
Whaaat, Miria, you don't even know that?
So... faithfully... duty... accomplishes...
What's wrong, Isaac?
Ahh, it's that!
Claire is Claire, so... she's a woman!
Amazing!